# Generated by https://opentdb.com
question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The common software-programming acronym \"I18N\" comes from the term \"Interlocalization\".",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Japan was part of the Allied Powers during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The very first recorded computer \"bug\" was a moth found inside a Harvard Mark II computer.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In \"Mario Kart 64\", Waluigi is a playable character.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The S in Harry S. Truman stands for \"Samuel\".",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Linus Torvalds created Linux and Git.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Soccer player Cristiano Ronaldo opened a museum dedicated to himself.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Faust is a playable character in \"Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator\".", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The word \"news\" originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A bear does NOT defecate during hibernation. ", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Vietnam is the only country in the world that starts with V. ",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "\"Ananas\" is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "An atom contains a nucleus.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "According to Norse mythology, Loki is a mother.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The term \"Spam\" came before the food product \"Spam\".",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: \"Justice rains from above!\"",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the TV series Red Dwarf, Kryten&#039;s full name is Kryten 2X4B-523P.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Centripedal force is an apparent force that acts outward on a body moving around a center, arising from the body&#039;s inertia.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The name of the attack \"Kamehameha\" in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Japan has left-hand side traffic.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A caterpillar has more muscles than humans do.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "Nazi Germany surrendered on Harry Truman&#039;s birthday while he was president.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Sugar contains fat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "\"Rich Uncle Pennybags\" from the board game \"Monopoly\" wears a monocle.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The ghosts in \"Pac-Man\" and \"Ms. Pac-Man\" have completely different behavior.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game \"Pocket Morty\" has a Morty called \"Pocket Mortys Morty\"?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "\"Return to Castle Wolfenstein\" was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William \"B.J.\" Blazkowicz.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In \"Star Trek: The Next Generation\", Data is the only android in existence.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Psychology is the science of behavior and mind.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song \"Do the Bartman\".",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In the \"Kagerou Daze\" series, Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "\"Green Eggs and Ham\" consists of only 50 different words.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In career mode of \"Need for Speed: Underground 2\", the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Venus of Willendorf is one of the earliest works of art, depicting the planets Mars and Venus embrace in the heavens at night.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There is an island in Japan called \u014ckunoshima, A.K.A. \"Rabbit Island\", so named because of it&#039;s huge population of rabbits.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "\"Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.\" is a grammatically correct sentence.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In \"Avatar: The Last Airbender\" and \"The Legend of Korra\", Lavabending is a specialized bending technique of Firebending.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "\"Resident Evil 7\" is the first first-person Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In \"Space Station 13\",  the station has a clown aboard it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
